Guide to the American Newspaper Repository Collection, 1852-2004 RL.10057
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
American Newspaper Repository collection
1852-2004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
American Newspaper Repository
RL.10057
1200 Linear Feet 12,000 items
The American Newspaper Repository was founded in 1999 as a 501(c)(3) non-profit corporation in order to save a unique collection of original newspapers that would otherwise have been destroyed or dispersed, and to preserve and make available these landmarks of American publishing. Nicholson Baker, author of numerous fiction and nonfiction works, including writings on libraries, founded and served as director of the Repository in conjunction with research for his 2001 release, Double Fold: Libraries and the Assault on Paper. The collection consists of approximately five thousand newspaper volumes (plus several thousand unbound newspapers), most of which came, directly or indirectly, from the British Library. There are long runs of major domestic newspapers as well as many foreign language and immigrant papers, such as the Yiddish Forward, the Irish World, and the Greek Atlantis, trade journals, Communist papers such as the Daily Worker, and other political papers. Many of these runs apparently exist nowhere else in the original format.
Separated Materials
A number of newspaper titles have been separated and cataloged individually in the library catalog. To locate these titles, search for "American Newspaper Repository" in the catalog.
Provenance
The American Newspaper Repository collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2003 and 2005.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Historical Note
The American Newspaper Repository was founded in 1999 as a 501(c)(3) non-profit corporation in order to save a unique collection of original newspapers that would otherwise have been destroyed or dispersed, and to preserve and make available these landmarks of American publishing. Nicholson Baker, author of numerous fiction and nonfiction works, including writings on libraries, founded and served as director of the Repository in conjunction with research for his 2001 release, Double Fold: Libraries and the Assault on Paper.
Collection Overview
The American Newspaper Repository collection consists of approximately five thousand newspaper volumes (plus unbound newspapers), most of which came, directly or indirectly, from the British Library. There are long runs of major domestic newspapers as well as many foreign language and immigrant papers, such as the Yiddish Forward, the Irish World, and the Greek Atlantis, trade journals, Communist papers such as the Daily Worker, and other political papers. Many of these runs apparently exist nowhere else in the original format.
A number of newspaper titles have been separated from the collection and cataloged individually in the library catalog. To locate these titles, search for "American Newspaper Repository" in the catalog.
- Amerika (Brooklyn, NY), 1946-1951, 1
  - Amerika (Brooklyn, NY), 1946 Jan. 4 - 1946 Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 25)
    Scope and Contents note
    [Note: Missing 1946 Aug. 16-23]
  - Amerika (Brooklyn, NY), 1947 Jan.-July; wrapped bundle (Box 25)
    [Note: Missing 1947 Jan. 10, June 13]
  - Amerika (Brooklyn, NY), 1948 Sept.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 25)
  - Amerika (Brooklyn, NY), 1949 - 1951 Apr. 13; wrapped bundle (Box 14)
    [Note: Missing 1949 Feb. 4, Mar. 2, Dec. 16; 1951 Jan. 12, Mar. 23]
- Atlantis, 1895-1925, 2
  - Atlantis, 1895 Mar.-1896 Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4975)
  - Atlantis, 1897-1898; bound volume (Volume 4978)
  - Atlantis, 1899-1900; bound volume (Volume 4976)
  - Atlantis, 1902 Jan.-Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4993)
  - Atlantis, 1902 Mar.-1903 Feb.; bound volume (Volume 4997)
  - Atlantis, 1903 Mar.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4998)
  - Atlantis, 1904 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4994)
  - Atlantis, 1904 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3863)
  - Atlantis, 1905 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 3865)
  - Atlantis, 1905 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3864)
  - Atlantis, 1906 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 3867)
  - Atlantis, 1906 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3866)
  - Atlantis, 1907 Jan.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3869)
  - Atlantis, 1907 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3868)
  - Atlantis, 1908 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3871)
  - Atlantis, 1908 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3870)
  - Atlantis, 1908 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3873)
  - Atlantis, 1908 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3872)
  - Atlantis, 1909 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3875)
  - Atlantis, 1909 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3874)
  - Atlantis, 1909 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 4547)
  - Atlantis, 1909 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3876)
  - Atlantis, 1910 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3821)
  - Atlantis, 1910 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3820)
  - Atlantis, 1910 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3823)
  - Atlantis, 1910 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3822)
  - Atlantis, 1911 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3825)
  - Atlantis, 1911 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3824)
  - Atlantis, 1911 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3827)
  - Atlantis, 1911 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3826)
  - Atlantis, 1912 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3829)
  - Atlantis, 1912 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3839)
  - Atlantis, 1912 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3828)
  - Atlantis, 1912 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3831)
  - Atlantis, 1913 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3830)
  - Atlantis, 1913 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3833)
  - Atlantis, 1913 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3832)
  - Atlantis, 1913 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3834)
  - Atlantis, 1914 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 5721)
  - Atlantis, 1914 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3835)
  - Atlantis, 1914 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 5722)
  - Atlantis, 1914 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3837)
  - Atlantis, 1915 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3849)
  - Atlantis, 1915 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3848)
  - Atlantis, 1915 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3851)
  - Atlantis, 1915 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3850)
  - Atlantis, 1916 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3853)
  - Atlantis, 1916 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3852)
  - Atlantis, 1916 July-Aug.; bound volume (Volume 3855)
  - Atlantis, 1917 Mar.-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3854)
  - Atlantis, 1917 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3857)
  - Atlantis, 1918 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 3856)
  - Atlantis, 1918 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3860)
  - Atlantis, 1918 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3859)
  - Atlantis, 1919 Jan.-Apr.; bound volume (Volume 4550)
  - Atlantis, 1919 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3858)
  - Atlantis, 1919 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3861)
  - Atlantis, 1919 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3862)
  - Atlantis, 1920 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 4996)
  - Atlantis, 1920 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 4991)
  - Atlantis, 1920 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 4559)
  - Atlantis, 1920 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4990)
  - Atlantis, 1921 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 4995)
  - Atlantis, 1921 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 4992)
  - Atlantis, 1921 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 4987)
  - Atlantis, 1921 Oct. - 1921 Dec. 29; bound volume (Volume 4984)
  - Atlantis, 1922 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 4989)
  - Atlantis, 1922 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 4988)
  - Atlantis, 1922 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 4986)
  - Atlantis, 1922 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4985)
  - Atlantis, 1923 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3838)
  - Atlantis, 1923 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3836)
  - Atlantis, 1923 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 4983)
  - Atlantis, 1923 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4982)
  - Atlantis, 1924 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3841)
  - Atlantis, 1924 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3840)
  - Atlantis, 1924 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3843)
  - Atlantis, 1924 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3842)
  - Atlantis, 1925 Jan.-Mar.; bound volume (Volume 3845)
  - Atlantis, 1925 Apr.-June; bound volume (Volume 3844)
  - Atlantis, 1925 July-Sept.; bound volume (Volume 3847)
  - Atlantis, 1925 Oct.-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 3846)
- Atlantis (New York), 1922-1944, 3
  - Atlantis (New York), 1922; wrapped bundle (Box 601)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1925; wrapped bundle (Box 602)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1923-1924; wrapped bundle (Box 1185)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1926; wrapped bundle (Box 1173)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1926 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 114)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1926 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 73)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1926 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 95)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1926 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 85)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1927; wrapped bundle (Box 1173)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1927 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 105)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1927 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 115)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1927 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 124)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1927 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 106)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1928; wrapped bundle (Box 600)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1928 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 126)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1928 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 125)
    [Note: Missing June 28-30]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1928 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 107)
    [Note: Missing July 1-2]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1928 Oct.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 108)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1929; wrapped bundle (Box 1174)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1929 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 117)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1929 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 116)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1929 July - 1929 Sept 15; wrapped bundle (Box 127)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1930; wrapped bundle (Box 1174)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1930 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 109)
    [Note: Missing Mar. 19-23]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1930 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 128)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1930 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 91)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1930 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 119)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1930 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 102)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1931; wrapped bundle (Box 599)
    [Note: Missing Oct. 1931]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1931 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 86)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1931 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 96)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1931 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 98)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1931 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 97)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1931 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 88)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1932; wrapped bundle (Box 599)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1932 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 87)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1932 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 75)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1932 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 111)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1932 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 110)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1932 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 120)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1933 Sep.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 99)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1933 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 74)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1933 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 101)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1933 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 100)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1933 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 90)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1934 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 89)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1934 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 78)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1934 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 77)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1934 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 76)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1934 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 118)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1934 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 130)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1935 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1846)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1935 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1848)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1935 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1837)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1935 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1850)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1935 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1847)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1936 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1849)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1936 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1852)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1936 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1851)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1936 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1840)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1936 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1838)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1936 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1839)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1936 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1804)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1937 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1806)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1937 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1856)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1937 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1803)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1937 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1823)
    [Note: Missing July 27-29]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1937 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1824)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1937 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1816)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1938 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1815)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1938 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1825)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1938 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1808)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1938 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1807)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1938 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1805)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1938 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1844)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1939 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1859)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1939 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1855)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1939 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1828)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1939 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1827)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1939 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1826)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1939 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1819)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1940 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1818)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1940 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1817)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1940 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1811)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1940 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1810)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1940 Sept.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1809)
    [Note: Imperfect]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1941 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1830)
    [Note: Missing Jan. 28-29]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1941 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1829)
    [Note: Missing Mar. 26-30]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1941 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1822)
    [Note: Missing May 30-31, June 1-3]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1941 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1821)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1941 Sept.-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1820)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1941 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1845)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1942 Jan.-Feb.; wrapped bundle (Box 1814)
    [Note: Missing Jan. 4-8]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1942 Mar.-Apr.; wrapped bundle (Box 1813)
    [Note: Missing Apr. 9-13, 24-28]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1942 May-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1812)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1942 July-Aug.; wrapped bundle (Box 1832)
    [Note: Missing July 22-26]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1942 Sept.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1831)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1943 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1841)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1943 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1857)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1943 July-Oct.; wrapped bundle (Box 1853)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1943 Nov.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1842)
    [Note: Missing Nov. 9-23, Dec. 7]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1944 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1858)
    [Note: Missing Mar. 2-25]
  - Atlantis (New York), 1944 Apr.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1854)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1944 July-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1843)
  - Atlantis (New York), 1944 Oct. - 1944 Nov. 21; wrapped bundle (Box 1881)
- Auclair, 1896-1897, 4
  - Auclair, 1896-1897; volume in box (Box 1698)
- Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1940-1973, 5
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1940 Jan.-Mar.; volume (Volume 5667)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1940 Apr.-June; volume (Volume 5668)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1940 July-Sept.; volume (Volume 5692)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1940 Oct.-Dec.; volume (Volume 5694)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1941 Jan.-Mar.; volume (Volume 5695)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1941 Apr.-June; volume (Volume 5696)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1941 July-Sept.; volume (Volume 5697)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1941 Oct.-Dec.; volume (Volume 5698)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1942 Jan. 2-Mar. 27; volume (Volume 5665)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1942 Apr.-June; volume (Volume 5666)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1942 July-Sept.; volume (Volume 5691)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1942 Oct.-Dec.; volume (Volume 5684)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1943 Jan.-Mar.; volume (Volume 5683)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1943 Apr.-June; volume (Volume 5681)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1943 July-Sept.; volume (Volume 5680)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1943 Oct.-Dec.; volume (Volume 5704)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1944 Jan. 7 - 1944 Mar.; volume (Volume 5690)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1944 Apr. 7-June 30; volume (Volume 5703)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1944 July 7-Sept. 29; volume (Volume 5702)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1944 Oct. 6-Dec. 29; volume (Volume 5669)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1945 Jan.-Mar.; volume (Volume 5674)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1945 Apr.-June; volume (Volume 5675)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1945 July-Sept.; volume (Volume 5673)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1945 Oct.-Dec.; volume (Volume 5672)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1946 Jan.-Mar.; volume (Volume 5679)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1946 Apr.-June; volume (Volume 5677)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1946 July-Sept.; volume (Volume 5676)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1946 Oct.-Dec.; volume (Volume 5678)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1947 Jan.-Mar.; volume (Volume 5670)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1947 Apr.-June; volume (Volume 5699)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1947 July-Sept.; volume (Volume 5671)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1947 Oct.-Dec.; volume (Volume 5693)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1948 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_8)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1948 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_3)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1949 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_2)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1949 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_4)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1950; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_19)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1951; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_20)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1952 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_14)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1952 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_11)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1953 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_15)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1953 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_5)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1954 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_6)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1954 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_7)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1955 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_38)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1955 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_1)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1956 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_12)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1956 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_13)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1957 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_37)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1957 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_36)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1958 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_10)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1958 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_37)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1959 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_9)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1959 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_6)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1960 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_1)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1960 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_18)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1961; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_16)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1962 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_36)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1962 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_7)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1963 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_10)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1963 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_34)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1964 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_11)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1964 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_18)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1965 Jan.-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_12)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1965 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_5)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1966; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_17)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1967 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_9)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1967 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_15)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1968 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_3)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1968 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_8)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1969 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_4)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1969 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_13)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1970 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_14)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1970 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_38)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1971; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_34)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1972; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_35)
  - Aufbau (New York, N.Y.), 1973; wrapped bundle (Box 05/038_2)
- Aurore, 1896-1897, 1899, 6
  - Aurore, 1896-1897; volume in box (Box 1698)
  - Aurore, 1899 Sept. 22; volume in box (Box 1685)
- Autorité, 1896-1897, 7
  - Autorité, 1896-1897; volume in box (Box 1698)
- Barron's, 1926-1930, 8
  - Barron's, 1926-1927; bound volume (Volume 4727)
  - Barron's, 1927-1928 June; bound volume (Volume 4723)
  - Barron's, 1928 July-Dec.; bound volume (Volume 4724)
  - Barron's, 1929; bound volume (Volume 4726)
  - Barron's, 1929; bound volume (Volume 4725)
  - Barron's, 1930 Jan.-June; bound volume (Volume 4722)
- Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1930-1939, 1942-1946, 9
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1930 July-Dec; wrapped bundle (Box 1297)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1931 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1293)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1931 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1306)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1932 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1301)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1932 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1290)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1933 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1294)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1933 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1307)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1934 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1302)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1934 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1298)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1935 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1295)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1935 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1303)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1936 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1291)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1936 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1299)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1937 Jan.-June.; wrapped bundle (Box 1310)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1937 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1308)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1938 Jan.-June; wrapped bundle (Box 1304)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1938 July-Dec.; wrapped bundle (Box 1305)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1939 Jan.-Mar.; wrapped bundle (Box 1305)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1942; wrapped bundle (Box 1309)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1943; wrapped bundle (Box 1300)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1944; wrapped bundle (Box 1289)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1945; wrapped bundle (Box 1296)
  - Barron's, the national financial weekly, 1946 Jan.-Sept.; wrapped bundle (Box 1292)
- Boston Globe, USA Today, Wall Street Journal, 1989-2000, 10
  Scope and Contents